symantec-norton.com 2015-06-23

# Norton Products by Symantec | Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy adheres to the US Safe Harbor privacy principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement. We are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of this site's visitors as well as personal information by following responsible information handling practices in keeping with privacy laws.

**_Anonymous Access_**

You can access and browse our website without disclosing _any_ of your personal data. We do not collect _any_ kind of personal information.

**_Use of Cookies_**

Cookies are small text files containing a string of characters. They are placed on your computer by some websites you visit and are used to uniquely identify your browser. Cookies do not impart personal files or information such as your real name and address. However, they do improve the quality of the service provided to you by storing user preferences and tracking user trends.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset yours to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent to your computer. Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information contained in a cookie is only disclosed or shared for advertising purposes and/or improving a user's visit of a particular website.

Symantec-Norton.com uses cookies for advertising purposes. No sensitive personal information is stored in cookies and your privacy is never at risk. Just know that:

\- Third party vendors, including Google, show ads on the Internet that redirect users to this website.  
\- Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on visitors' previous visits on this website.  
\- Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Vistirs can also choose to opt out of any third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Also, all Symantec online stores use cookies. Since you will be redirected to the store corresponding to your country in order to make your purchase, we want to make sure you are aware of this fact.

**_Choice_**

We do _not_ ask for your credit card information on our site. However, it will be required on the Symantec online store to which you will be redirected for your purchase. Rest assured that this information will be encrypted on Symantec’s secure servers.

Symantec Corporation has its own, very strict [Privacy Policy](http://www.symantec.com/about/profile/privacypolicy/index.jsp), which explains how personal information entered on a particular Symantec web property is handled. Please refer to it should you have any concerns.

Finally, when you send an email or other communication to our offices, we may retain these communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We will not share in any way (sell, rent, exchange or give) any information contained in these communications with other companies. Similarly, we will not share in any way (sell, rent, exchange or give) any email address used to communicate with us with other companies.

**_Ongoing Relevancy_**

We regularly review our policies and procedures to ensure we remain current with changing laws and evolving public expectations.

We welcome comments and questions on our privacy policy. If you need to reach out to us about our privacy practices, you can simply send an email to: [privacy@symantec-norton.com](mailto:privacy@symantec-norton.com). 

Please be aware that due to the evolving nature of the technologies we use to communicate with you, we may occasionally update this policy. However, notices for all revisions will be posted on our site in clear view.
